# Tasha Salgado 1911eT

www.tashasalgado.design | tasha@tashasalgado.design | 510.798.6442 | Fort Worth, Tx

## about

As a **UX designer**, I combine creative and usability viewpoints that result in real-world solutions for Web and Mobile applications.

My user-centered process aids in providing a compelling user experience to improve brand loyalty, customer retention and seamless experiences for users.

## education

**Bloc** | 2018-2019 UX UI Design & Front-End Development Apprenticeship

Texas Woman's
University | 2018-2020
BS Sociology

## skills

User Research
Persona Creation
Interviews & Surveys
Card Sorting
User-centered Design
Sketching
Wireframing
Protoyping
Competative Analysis
User Stories
User Flows
Usability Testing
User Interface Design
Basic HTML & CSS

## projects

#### **PUSH | iOS Prototype**

- Designed a simple solution for cloud storage users who need extra security and easier organizing options.
- This app features digital security codes for file sharing
- Figma, Invision, Usability Hub
   Invision Prototype: https://invis.io/4YPSV8KQDWM

#### Health Hooch | Web & Mobile E-commerce Design

- Designed a prototype e-commerce store and mobile app for an entreprenuer launching a homemade line of herbal tonics.
- Logo Design & Branding
- This protoypes included custom product mockups.
- Figma, Invision, Usability Hub Invision Prototype:

#### Positive Actions International | Website Re-Design

- Re-designed this website for updated and modern aesthetics as well as smoother navigation and better conversion.
- This app features digital security codes for file sharing and folder/categories only for organizing.
- Figma, Invision, Usability Hub
  Website: https://www.positiveactionsinternational.com/

## experience

### **UX Design Apprenticeship**

6.2018 - Present

Bloc, Remote

- Developed fundamental design skills with the guidance of seasoned mentors
- Designed web applications using the full UX process, Visual Design and Frontend Development for projects

#### **Real Estate Agent**

2.2017 - 9.2017

First Class RE, Remote

- Demonstrated excellent negotiating skills as well as attention to detail and clients' needs resulting in 100 percent customer satisfaction.
- Successfully guided first time homebuyers and renters through the rental and purchase process of several properties.

